/*global angular */
/*

        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{9}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{13}}{\\input{36}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{9}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{36}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{9}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\fracstr{36}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\fracstr{36}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{36}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{36}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{13}}{\\input{36}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{10}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{10}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{12}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\fracstr{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{12}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{7}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{52}}{\\input{21}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{7}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{21}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{7}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{24}}{\\fracstr{21}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{28}}{\\fracstr{21}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{24}}{\\fracstr{21}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{28}}{\\fracstr{21}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{52}}{\\input{21}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{24}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{15}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{107}}{\\input{120}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{15}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{120}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{15}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{75}}{\\fracstr{120}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{32}}{\\fracstr{120}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{75}}{\\fracstr{120}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{32}}{\\fracstr{120}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{107}}{\\input{120}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{65}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{24}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{45}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{45}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{65}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{49}}{\\input{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{60}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{24}}{\\fracstr{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{20}}{\\fracstr{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{24}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{49}}{\\input{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{27}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{20}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{6}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{16}}{\\fracstr{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{16}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{27}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{57}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{12}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{15}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{28}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{14}}{\\fracstr{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{28}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{14}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{57}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});*/

/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').service('data10_1', ['dataUtils', function (dataUtils) {
    var desc = {
			title: '10.1 Adding Unlike Fractions',
			path: '10.1-adding-unlike-fractions',
            children: []
        },
	        template = {
            twoFractions: {
                title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
                children: [{
                    title: 'Main Answer',
                    children: [{
						problem: '\\html{&nbsp;}',
						answer: '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:550%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\grp{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}}{border-bottom-with-padding}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:300%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\input{$sumNum}}{\\input{$answerDen}}}}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": false,
							"workbook": true
						}
                    }]
                }, {
                    title: 'Workbook',
                    children: [{
						problem: '\\rowgrp'
						+'{\\str{Determine the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}'
						+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
						+'{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}'
						+'{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}'
						+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}}',
						answer: '\\input{$answerDen}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\str{The LCD of $firstDen and $secondDen is $answerDen.}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\str{\xA0 Answer: \xA0 $answerDen}}{help-answer-text}}'
						},
                    }, {
						problem: '\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }',
						answer: '\\rowgrp'						
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\input{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\input{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\rowgrp{\\str{Answer:}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{help-answer-text}}'
						}
                    }, {
						problem: '\\str{Add the fractions: }',
						answer: '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:550%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\grp{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}{border-bottom-with-padding}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:300%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\input{$sumNum}}{\\input{$answerDen}}}}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\row{\\html{\xA0}}{\\sign{\xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{row{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}{border-bottom-with-padding}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css'
							+'{\\row{\\html{\xA0}}{\\sign{\xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$sumNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}{help-answer-text-tight}'
						}
                    }]
                }]
            },
			threeFractions: {
                title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
                children: [{
                    title: 'Main Answer',
                    children: [{
						problem: '\\html{&nbsp;}',
						answer: '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:550%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:550%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\grp{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdNum}}{\\fracstr{$thirdDen}}}}{border-bottom-with-padding}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:300%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\input{$sumNum}}{\\input{$answerDen}}}}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": false,
							"workbook": true
						}
                    }]
                }, {
                    title: 'Workbook',
                    children: [{
						problem: '\\rowgrp'
						+'{\\str{Determine the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}'
						+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
						+'{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}'
						+'{\\str{\xA0 , \xA0}}'
						+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}'
						+'{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}'
						+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdNum}}{\\fracstr{$thirdDen}}}}',
						answer: '\\input{$answerDen}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\str{The LCD of $firstDen, $secondDen, and $thirdDen is $answerDen.}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\str{\xA0 Answer: \xA0 $answerDen}}{help-answer-text}}'
						},
                    }, {
						problem: '\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }',
						answer: '\\rowgrp'						
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\input{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\input{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdNum}}{\\fracstr{$thirdDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\input{$thirdAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstNum}}{\\fracstr{$firstDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondNum}}{\\fracstr{$secondDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdNum}}{\\fracstr{$thirdDen}}}'
							+'{\\sign{=}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\rowgrp{\\str{Answer:}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{help-answer-text}}'
						}
                    }, {
						problem: '\\str{Add the fractions: }',
						answer: '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:550%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:550%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{\\grp{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}{border-bottom-with-padding}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\grp{\\html{<span style="font-size:300%;">&nbsp;</span>}}{\\frac{\\input{$sumNum}}{\\input{$answerDen}}}}',
						controls: {
							"checkAnswer": true,
							"help": '\\rowgrp'
							+'{\\row{\\html{\xA0}}{\\sign{\xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$firstAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\row{\\html{\xA0}}{\\sign{\xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$secondAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css{row{\\sign{+}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$thirdAnswerNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}{border-bottom-with-padding}}'
							+'{\\html{&nbsp;}}'
							+'{\\css'
							+'{\\row{\\html{\xA0}}{\\sign{\xA0}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{$sumNum}}{\\fracstr{$answerDen}}}}{help-answer-text-tight}'
						}
                    }]
                }]
            }
        },
        data = [
            { firstNum: '1', firstDen: '4', secondNum: '3', secondDen: '5', firstAnswerNum: '5', secondAnswerNum: '12', sumNum: '17', answerDen: '20', template: 'twoFractions' },
            { firstNum: '1', firstDen: '9', secondNum: '1', secondDen: '4', firstAnswerNum: '4', secondAnswerNum: '9', sumNum: '13', answerDen: '36', template: 'twoFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '2', firstDen: '5', secondNum: '1', secondDen: '2', firstAnswerNum: '4', secondAnswerNum: '5', sumNum: '9', answerDen: '10', template: 'twoFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '3', firstDen: '4', secondNum: '1', secondDen: '6', firstAnswerNum: '9', secondAnswerNum: '2', sumNum: '11', answerDen: '12', template: 'twoFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '8', firstDen: '7', secondNum: '4', secondDen: '3', firstAnswerNum: '24', secondAnswerNum: '28', sumNum: '52', answerDen: '21', template: 'twoFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '3', firstDen: '8', secondNum: '1', secondDen: '3', firstAnswerNum: '9', secondAnswerNum: '8', sumNum: '17', answerDen: '24', template: 'twoFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '9', firstDen: '8', secondNum: '5', secondDen: '6', firstAnswerNum: '27', secondAnswerNum: '20', sumNum: '47', answerDen: '24', template: 'twoFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '1', firstDen: '2', secondNum: '1', secondDen: '4', thirdNum: '1', thirdDen: '6', firstAnswerNum: '6', secondAnswerNum: '3', thirdAnswerNum: '2', sumNum: '11', answerDen: '12', template: 'threeFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '3', firstDen: '10', secondNum: '1', secondDen: '4', thirdNum: '4', thirdDen: '5', firstAnswerNum: '6', secondAnswerNum: '5', thirdAnswerNum: '16', sumNum: '27', answerDen: '20', template: 'threeFractions' },
			{ firstNum: '5', firstDen: '4', secondNum: '7', secondDen: '3', thirdNum: '7', thirdDen: '6', firstAnswerNum: '15', secondAnswerNum: '28', thirdAnswerNum: '14', sumNum: '57', answerDen: '12', template: 'threeFractions' }
			
        ];

    return dataUtils.build(desc, template, data);
}]);
